https://yogatree.com.au/privacy-policy

Yoga Tree Privacy PolicyThere are places at our sites where you can share your personal information with us and where you can communicate with others.Yoga Tree (ABN 82 633 965 787) (we, our, us or Yoga Tree) recognises that your privacy is very important to you. Providing your personal information is an act of trust that we take very seriously. We comply with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (Privacy Act) and the applicable Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act when handling personal information. We will not sell, trade, give or rent any information obtained from you to a third party, unless you have specifically agreed to this occurring. Further Information can be found at the Government Privacy web site: www.privacy.gov.au.Registration and Collection of InformationSome sites let you register with us and sometimes registration is required before certain site features can be used.We collect personal information for the purposes of delivering our products and services and communicating with Customers regarding our services through the Yoga Tree website located at www.yogatree.com.au (Website). We collect personal information:From users – when they register an enquiry, book a class through the online booking form or purchase a Phoenix Yoga Studios membership;From suppliers or third parties – when they are engaged to supply services to us, provide information to us or invoice us for the provision of services;When we receive enquiries through the Website and when the Website is otherwise accessed or used.The kind of personal information we may collect will depend on who you are (e.g. a customer or supplier) and the nature of your interaction with us, and may include your full name, email address, company name, billing information and other personal information. If you do not provide us with all the information we request, we may not be able to deliver our services.You may be assigned a site username and/or password. We use this to communicate with you and provide a personalised experience.ConsentBy engaging us or registering your details on our Website, agreeing to the Customer Terms and Conditions or Supplier Terms and Conditions and/or using the Website or supplying documents to us, you consent to us collecting, using and disclosing your personal information for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy.Automatic Data CollectionOur websites have features that automatically collect information and show personalised user preferences.Some of our sites use cookies. These are small data files containing information about the user that are stored on the user’s hard drive.Cookies are used to make login to our sites easier (like remembering usernames and passwords) and to track movements to enhance your experience online.If users reject cookies, they may be limited in using some areas of our sites.For internal purposes, we may gather information (date, time, browser type, navigation history, and IP address) for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, system administration, and to gather demographic information.In the course of serving advertisements to the Website (if any), third-party advertisers or ad servers may place or recognise a unique cookie on your browser. The use of cookies by such third party advertisers or ad servers is not subject to this Privacy Policy, but is subject to their own respective privacy policies.SecurityYour security is extremely important to us. We store your personal information securely to protect it from loss, misuse, unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.Upon request, we will delete any information that you no longer want us to hold.Third Party Websites (Links)We may provide links to non-Yoga Tree sites.Please note that by following a link on our site that directs you to our partners, advertisers and other third party websites, your activity on the third party website will be governed by that website’s privacy policy. Please ensure you review these policies before submitting personal information to these websites as we do not accept responsibility or liability for policies pertaining to third party websites.Communication With UsWhen you contact us, we retain your email and contact information to serve you best.Newsletter and Other Communications From UsRegistered users and customers may receive newsletters or other email communications from us.When you sign up for newsletters, we ask for contact information (name, email address, demographic and profile information). We use this information to learn about you so we can better serve you and to send e-newsletter announcements about our administration details.We offer guests the choice to receive mailings from other organisations that we think you will like. Recipients of our mailings can unsubscribe by following instructions that appear at the end of the e-newsletter.Interactive Community FeaturesOur sites may offer interactive and community features (message boards, chat, email accounts, instant messaging, profiles, personal homepages, etc.). This information may be publicly available.When you voluntarily disclose personal information (user name, email address, phone number) information can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited communications.Users are solely responsible for the content they share on public forums.Contests, Surveys, FundraisersWe may have contests, surveys and fundraisers on our sites.When you participate, we request contact information (name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, demographic, and profile information).We use the information to conduct the promotion (for example, to contact you if you are the winner).We may partner with sponsors to offer contests, surveys and fundraisers, and may share your information with them so they can contact the winners and/or participants.We may also use the information to send you newsletters and other information we think may be of interest. Recipients can unsubscribe by following instructions that may appear at the end of the email newsletter.With Whom Your Information Is SharedWe may share your information with others if you choose to let us.We do not share your personal information with other companies. We only share it with our agents who provide service to you and agree to only use it for that purpose and promise to keep it secure and confidential.Yoga Tree, including all its business units, subsidiaries, affiliates and sites, companies we may merge with (merging our assets, products, sites, operations, ect.) will also be able to access your data in order to continue to serve you.We offer you opt-in and opt-out choices.We use aggregate demographic information about our audience (like gender or geographic location, but not individual data) for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting.We disclose information when required by law.AccessIf your personal information changes, we will make that change in the system to stay current.You can request, and we will provide you with access to, any personal information we hold about you (subject to any applicable legal exceptions). Please also let us know if you have any concerns or complaints about the way we are handling your personal information so we can address them.Transfer In Certain CircumstancesIf there is a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganisation or liquidation of us then, in our sole discretion, we may transfer, sell or assign personal information collected to one or more relevant third parties.PricesAll prices are listed in Australian dollars and include GST.In the event that a product is mistakenly listed at an incorrect price, Yoga Tree reserves the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for a product listed at the incorrect price. Yoga Tree reserves the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your account charged. If your account has already been charged for the purchase and your order is cancelled, Yoga Tree shall issue a credit to your account in the amount of the incorrect price.Privacy Policy ChangesYoga Tree reserves the right to modify and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. Depending on the nature of the change, we may announce the change on the home page of the Website or by email (if we have your email address). However, in any event, by continuing to use the Website following any changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time, in whole or part, you must terminate your use of the Website.We encourage you to review this policy from time to time.ContactIf you have any questions or complaints about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us.Yoga Tree5 Horne Street, Elsternwick VIC 3185info@yogatree.com.au a 5 Horne St. Elsternwick VIC p (03) 9532 7418 e info@yogatree.com.au© 2020 Yoga Tree. Registration Form | Privacy Policy | Student Ts & Cs | Download Direct Debit Form | Designed by: Sanjay Designs
Online ClassesNew?New Student RegistrationClass TimesPricingEventsShamanic Breathwork – Starts 22 NOVAboutOur MissionTeam YTContactMember Login
